[{"answer": "No, I'm not. I'm just really busy", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What do you mean? What kind of person am I", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You can put those in my box.  I'll look at them tomorrow", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Righ", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You just woke up this morning and suddenly decided to run for president", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Thought what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "But other people can see them too", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, I do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Easy, tiger.  Come by after school. I'll leave my friend with the sitter", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Three twent", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I guess you know why you're her", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "A travesty.  Huh.  That's interesting, because I think you did it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Okay.  But is this about the posters", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Okay.  Because I know who did it.  So.. I'll just be outside", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Looks at her skeptically  doesn't say a word", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And when did you do it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Which door", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't believe you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Good luck to you too, my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Sherry... I love you", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It's the only true thing I know anymore", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "A mistake?  That was no mistake", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Me?  I took advantage of you?  You hugged me!  You kissed me!  You're the one who", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "But, they were there I counted 803 votes", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I didn't make a mistake. Every vote was there when you sac dow", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "My mother's buying me a new car for college", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well, I got in everywhere I applied, but that place is my first choice", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Election.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Doing what", "qsentId": 30}]